{
    "subject": "resource/Ron_Fenton",
    "predicate": "property/clubs",
    "object": "resource/Birmingham_City_F.C.",
    "human_readable": "Ron Fenton plays for Birmingham City F.C.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8502007722854614,
            "question": "Who plays for Birmingham City F.C.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5826880931854248,
            "question": "Name a player who belongs to Birmingham City F.C."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5645853281021118,
            "question": "What football club does Ron Fenton play for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5524065494537354,
            "question": "What sport does Ron Fenton play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5072303414344788,
            "question": "What is the name of the football club that Ron Fenton plays for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4426269829273224,
            "question": "Is Birmingham City F.C. a professional sports team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4211239814758301,
            "question": "Where does Ron Fenton play football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4184407889842987,
            "question": "Which team is Ron Fenton associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26331955194473267,
            "question": "Is Ron Fenton a footballer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.031174607574939728,
            "question": "Can you name a football club based in England?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ron Fenton plays for Birmingham City F.C.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3347_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ron Fenton a footballer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3347_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which team is Ron Fenton associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3347_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Ron Fenton play football?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3347_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3347_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3347_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3347_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3347_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3347_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3347_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3347_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3347_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3347_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3347_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n* The triple \"Ron Fenton plays for Birmingham City F.C.\" is partially correct, as it is mentioned in one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3347/re-ranker-msmarco/56.txt) that Ron Fenton played for Birmingham City, but not explicitly stated that he played for Birmingham City F.C. (which suggests a specific type of football club).\n* However, the document also mentions that he played for other teams, such as Burnley and Brentford, which are also types of football clubs.\n\nTherefore, my response is:\n\n{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Ronald Fenton played for Birmingham City, among other clubs. Therefore, the statement that Ron Fenton played for Birmingham City F.C. is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It contradicts information provided in section 2 where it states Fenton played for West Bromwich Albion in 1962, later playing for Birmingham City and finally Brentford. This implies that he played for Birmingham City before playing for Brentford, not the other way around.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}